Do you want to live a longer, healthier
life? Social media is full of people
claiming they already know how with
vitamins, supplements, injections,
hyperbaric chambers, red light masks.
There is no shortage of [music] products
promising to slow down aging. But, what
does real longevity look like? Business
Insider spoke to some of the hottest
rising stars making a real impact on
longevity research, [music]
medicine, and the funding behind it. One
of them is Morgan Levine, a scientist at
the billionaire-backed Altos [music]
Labs. She's developing AI world models
that simulate lab experiments,
potentially accelerating [music]
research into new ways to tackle aging.
Aging's probably one of the most
complex, [music] difficult problems you
can actually study in biology. So, I
actually think it needs something like
AI that's able to unravel these really
complex phenomenon. Then there's Jamie
Justice, who leads Xprize Healthspan,
which is a $101 million global
competition aimed at extending healthy
human life
>> [music]
>> by a decade. It's not a matter of
science fiction. It's a matter of what
tools do we have in front of us right
now. How do we develop this? How do we
do it sustainably, ethically, and for
the good of humanity?
>> [music]
>> These are just two of the
longevity-focused researchers, doctors,
and investors [music] we profiled in our
rising stars of longevity list. Experts
are saying it's a critical moment for
the longevity industry. It's [music] no
longer just biohackers promising
immortality. Check out the full list of
rising stars of longevity at Business
Insider.